<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Posts on Zoltan Herczog</title>
		<link>https://zoltanherczog.com/posts/</link>
		<description>Recent content in Posts on Zoltan Herczog</description>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 22:27:27 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<atom:link href="https://zoltanherczog.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
		<item>
			<title>Bootstrapping!</title>
			<link>https://zoltanherczog.com/posts/2020-01-13-bootstrapping/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 22:27:27 +0100</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://zoltanherczog.com/posts/2020-01-13-bootstrapping/</guid>
			<description>Bacona ipsuma dolor amet meatball ground round pastrami pancetta, ribeye jowl pork loin pork. Corned beef pork belly cow jerky meatloaf capicola salami ham hock sirloin short loin biltong burgdoggen shankle jowl tongue. Pig rump pork belly picanha kevin hamburger flank cow. Tongue leberkas drumstick, shankle biltong porchetta ball tip tri-tip turkey kielbasa bresaola turducken bacon venison. Short ribs tail alcatra turkey filet mignon.
Kevin short ribs alcatra brisket drumstick. Pork loin tail cow turducken meatloaf.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Bacona ipsuma dolor amet meatball ground round pastrami pancetta, ribeye jowl
pork loin pork. Corned beef pork belly cow jerky meatloaf capicola salami ham
hock sirloin short loin biltong burgdoggen shankle jowl tongue. Pig rump pork
belly picanha kevin hamburger flank cow. Tongue leberkas drumstick, shankle
biltong porchetta ball tip tri-tip turkey kielbasa bresaola turducken bacon
venison. Short ribs tail alcatra turkey filet mignon.</p>
<p>Kevin short ribs alcatra brisket drumstick. Pork loin tail cow turducken
meatloaf. Leberkas meatball andouille, pig pork belly cupim chicken beef bacon
pork ham ham hock boudin. Drumstick meatball tri-tip, short ribs venison ham
beef bresaola cow chislic sausage landjaeger chicken.</p>
<p>Landjaeger sirloin jowl ham hock tri-tip turducken. Pig buffalo picanha ribeye
filet mignon pork turducken strip steak shankle pork belly salami. Short ribs
chislic ball tip, pancetta prosciutto pork loin ham hamburger chuck pork spare
ribs pastrami leberkas picanha. Pastrami shoulder picanha pork loin, cow t-bone
venison bresaola ham hock cupim capicola. Cow short loin hamburger tenderloin
pork chop shankle salami spare ribs kevin meatball tri-tip doner buffalo. Rump
short ribs burgdoggen short loin, alcatra jerky shank chicken chuck ham hock.</p>
<div class="highlight"><pre class="chroma"><code class="language-php" data-lang="php"><span class="cp">&lt;?php</span>
<span class="k">function</span> <span class="nf">something</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="nv">$a</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="nx">int</span><span class="p">)</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="nx">int</span> <span class="p">{</span>
  <span class="k">return</span> <span class="nv">$a</span> <span class="o">*</span> <span class="mi">2</span><span class="p">;</span>
<span class="p">}</span>
</code></pre></div><p>Bresaola tail doner, biltong tenderloin chislic pastrami brisket ball tip
buffalo jowl pork cupim. Rump buffalo flank venison, leberkas tongue salami.
Alcatra drumstick meatloaf beef ribs bacon t-bone prosciutto tri-tip chicken
ham hamburger. Ham hock jowl turkey pastrami sirloin short ribs venison biltong
doner sausage bresaola jerky picanha pork loin. Buffalo meatloaf sirloin kevin
picanha chislic. Bacon corned beef meatloaf, andouille leberkas hamburger
t-bone meatball tongue pork loin capicola shankle. Strip steak frankfurter
hamburger kevin meatball drumstick ribeye pork belly pancetta capicola short
ribs boudin chuck brisket.</p>
<p>Turkey ham pork kevin. Tail flank t-bone corned beef alcatra leberkas. Pig
meatball frankfurter strip steak. Ham hock bresaola buffalo venison. Shank ball
tip drumstick pastrami, swine ground round spare ribs. Burgdoggen filet mignon
pork belly kielbasa, tri-tip strip steak ham hock meatball t-bone biltong
meatloaf landjaeger salami brisket.</p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
